

OBJECTIVE

Seeking an inside Sales Representative position with a vibrant company utilizing over 5 years sales experience, while utilizing my three (3) simple tactics (Think 80/20(Focus), Act 30/30 (Efficiency), and 90/10 Live (Accountability)) to contribute to the business and improve company revenues. In addition to, adopting my highly effective communication skills, demonstrated persuasive negotiations skills together with strong organizational skills to ensure consistent achievement of sales targets. A team player with a winning attitude and a passion for sales looking to make a significant contribution to company.

CONTACT

PHONE: 702-470-6800

ADDRESS: 4017 Forest Knoll Lane Las Vegas, Nevada 89129

EMAIL: roblesfamilyfirst@gmail.com

HOBBIES

I'm a full time soccer Dad, and Assistant Coach for a Nevada Soccer Club.

JAVIER ROBLES

Sales Representative

EDUCATION

Everest College

February, 2009 – February, 2011 Associates Degree, Criminal Justice

Cesar Chavez High School

September, 2000 – June, 2004 High School Diploma, General Studies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Logical Position- Digital Marketing Specialists

May 2019-Present

Logical Position is a growing marketing agency, that assist businesses achieve their highest potential. As an inside sales representative, I'm given the opportunity to select a niche, find leads and present our services and benefits to business owners telephonically. Direct and teach business owners on how to properly invest in the right digital marketing, while providing the best customer service.

Wyndham Destinations - Inside Sales Representative/Owner UpgradesNovember 2018-May 2019

After obtaining my Timeshare Agent License, I joined one of the leading vacation ownership company. Wherein, i connected with owners telephonically and educated them about them about their ownership. In addition, to discussing their future vacation plans, and ownership goals. In order to provide there best upgrading options.

Identifix -Market Area Representative

December, 2016–September, 2018

Telephonically generate leads and develop relationships to maintain sales pipeline of customers within my territory. Maintain knowledge of products and changes to drive sales and serve customer needs. Most importantly develop a full sales cycle including prospect, question/develop, propose, negotiate and close sales.

Advanced Auto Parts-Regional Sales Manager

July, 2015-December, 2016

Achieve regional sales objectives telephonically. Build and maintain rapport with customers together with educating customers of new products, and our service. In addition to surveying customer to provide the best customer service, and eventually closing deals.

Rent-A-Wheel- Store Manager

August, 2014-March, 2015

Making sure that my team and I provide the best customer service, which contributed to making our store profitable. Being part of Rent a Wheel gave me a huge opportunity to develop previous and new employees, to help them reach their full potential. That is why I was able to grow our store in 02/15 by 45,000 in agreement balance, which was a huge impact to the company.

SKILLS

